hallels.com 2018-12-02

# Hallels

### Privacy Policy

[Hallels.com]() is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders, to improve our web page, and to generate content. The following discloses what information our web site collects and what we do with it. This privacy statement is for informational purposes only and should not be viewed as a contract. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact webmaster at http://www.hallels.com/

  1. #### information collected and usage

When you connect to our web site, we are able to recognize the Internet (IP) address of your computer. We may use this IP address to help diagnose problems with our server or otherwise administer our Web site. This IP address may also be used to gather broad demographic information. Your IP address is never associated with you as an individual and never provided to another company or organization.

Our site may write a small data file called a cookie onto your computer No personal information is placed in this file. The file is removed when you exit your browser.

We do not collect your name or email address unless provided on a registration form, order form, survey form, or sent to us through an email. Our site\'s forms may ask or require you to give us contact information (such as email address), financial information (such as your account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (such as your zip code or age). We use this information to provide information, products, or services that you request. Any information collected is primarily for internal Hallels.com use and is not made available to any outside group or organization except other agencies or companies working with Hallels.com for the designated purposes.

Our web site contains links to other sites. We cannot be responsible for the privacy practices or the content of sites that do not belong to Hallels.com.

  2. #### policies for children (under the age of 13)

Hallels.com encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the activities offered on the Hallels.com web site. No personally identifiable information should be submitted to or posted at Hallels.com by visitors under 13 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian.

This web site does not solicit or allow children under 13 to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information. In the event that we ask for information online from children under the age of 13, we do not require personally identifiable information such as child\'s last name, city, or e-mail address.

If our Hallels.com staff receive e-mail from children under 13, we may contact the child under the following circumstances:

    1. to respond directly to the child\'s request on a one-time basis for a specific request from the child where it is not used to re-contact the child for other purposes,
    2. in order to request the name or online contact information of a parent for the sole purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing parental notification, and
    3. to respond more than once directly to a specific request from the child and not used to re-contact the child beyond the scope of that request (such as the case where a child requests a newsletter subscription). Where the information is used to contact the child more than once, Hallels.com uses reasonable efforts to provide parental notification.
  3. #### summary

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders, to improve our web page, to gather content, and to evaluate our resources . If you should have questions about our privacy policy, please contact us through our contact page.

  4. #### About Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>
